!function(e){function t(t){for(var c,l,a=t[0],i=t[1],s=t[2],d=0,y=[];d<a.length;d++)l=a[d],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(o,l)&&o[l]&&y.push(o[l][0]),o[l]=0;for(c in i)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(i,c)&&(e[c]=i[c]);for(u&&u(t);y.length;)y.shift()();return n.push.apply(n,s||[]),r()}function r(){for(var e,t=0;t<n.length;t++){for(var r=n[t],c=!0,a=1;a<r.length;a++){var i=r[a];0!==o[i]&&(c=!1)}c&&(n.splice(t--,1),e=l(l.s=r[0]))}return e}var c={},o={0:0},n=[];function l(t){if(c[t])return c[t].exports;var r=c[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(r.exports,r,r.exports,l),r.l=!0,r.exports}l.m=e,l.c=c,l.d=function(e,t,r){l.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:r})},l.r=function(e){"undefined"!=typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},l.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=l(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"==typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var r=Object.create(null);if(l.r(r),Object.defineProperty(r,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var c in e)l.d(r,c,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,c));return r},l.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e.default}:function(){return e};return l.d(t,"a",t),t},l.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},l.p="";var a=window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[],i=a.push.bind(a);a.push=t,a=a.slice();for(var s=0;s<a.length;s++)t(a[s]);var u=i;n.push([63,1]),r()}({11:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){r.d(t,"e",(function(){return p})),r.d(t,"c",(function(){return u})),r.d(t,"a",(function(){return d})),r.d(t,"b",(function(){return y}));var c,o=r(21);function n(e,t){var r=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var c=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(c=c.filter((function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable}))),r.push.apply(r,c)}return r}function l(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var r=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?n(Object(r),!0).forEach((function(t){a(e,t,r[t])})):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(r)):n(Object(r)).forEach((function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(r,t))}))}return e}function a(e,t,r){return t in e?Object.defineProperty(e,t,{value:r,enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0}):e[t]=r,e}(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var i,s,u=1,d="ìë°”ìŠ¤í¬ë¦½íŠ¸ í€´ì¦ˆ",y="quizScores",f={scores:{}},p=function(e){return{type:"SCORES",data:e}},k=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:f,t=arguments.length>1?arguments[1]:void 0;switch(t.type){case"SCORES":return o.a.setLocalStorage(y,t.data.scores),l({},e,{scores:t.data.scores});default:return e}},b=k;t.d=b,(i="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(i.register(u,"QUESTION_LIST","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(d,"HEADER_TITLE","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(y,"LOCAL_STORAGE_KEY","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(f,"initialState","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register("SCORES","SCORES","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(p,"scoresAction","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(k,"reducer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js"),i.register(b,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\main.js")),(s="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&s(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},21:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c;function o(e,t){for(var r=0;r<t.length;r++){var c=t[r];c.enumerable=c.enumerable||!1,c.configurable=!0,"value"in c&&(c.writable=!0),Object.defineProperty(e,c.key,c)}}r.d(t,"a",(function(){return a})),(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var n,l,a=function(){function e(){!function(e,t){if(!(e instanceof t))throw new TypeError("Cannot call a class as a function")}(this,e)}var t,r,c;return t=e,c=[{key:"getLocalStorage",value:function(e){return JSON.parse(window.localStorage.getItem(e))}},{key:"setLocalStorage",value:function(e,t){window.localStorage.setItem(e,JSON.stringify(t))}}],(r=null)&&o(t.prototype,r),c&&o(t,c),e}();(n="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&n.register(a,"Store","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\store\\Store.js"),(l="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&l(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},28:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var r;(r="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&r(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var c,o,n={intermediate:[{name:"Test1",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let result = 2009;\nconst func = (x = 262) => {\n  result = x;\n};\nfunc( null );",example:[{title:"null",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"262",key:1,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = 0 || 1 && 2 || 3;",example:[{title:"3",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:2,correct:""},{title:"0",key:3,correct:""},{title:"1",key:4,correct:""},{title:"2",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const plus = +0;\nconst minus = -0;\nconst result = plus === minus;",example:[{title:"false",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const result = "1" == 1;',example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const value = new Set( [ 1, 1, 2, 3, 2, 3 ] );\nconst result = [ ...value ];",example:[{title:"[1]",key:0,correct:""},{title:"112323",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[1,1,2,3,2,3]",key:2,correct:""},{title:"[1,2,3]",key:3,correct:"correct"},{title:"[1,2,3,1,2,3]",key:4,correct:""}],correct:3},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const getA = () => 1;\nconst getB = () => 2;\nconst getC = () => 3;\nconst result = ( getA(), getB(), getC() );",example:[{title:"3",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"1",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"6",key:3,correct:""},{title:"2",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 10, 15, 20, 25, 30 ];\nconst result = array.find( v => v > 15 );",example:[{title:"20",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"2",key:1,correct:""},{title:"15",key:2,correct:""},{title:"3",key:3,correct:""},{title:"1",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"class User {\n  getName() {}\n}\n\nconst result = typeof User;",example:[{title:"string",key:1,correct:""},{title:"object",key:2,correct:""},{title:"class",key:3,correct:""},{title:"prototype",key:4,correct:""},{title:"function",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test2",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const map = v => v * v;\nconst array = Array.from( [ 1, 2, 3 ], map );",example:[{title:"1,4,9",key:1,correct:""},{title:"149",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"14",key:2,correct:""},{title:"1,2,3",key:3,correct:""},{title:"123",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nconst result = 3 in Array;",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"true",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const func = function (x, y = 4) {\n  return x + y;\n};\n\nconst result = func( 2 );",example:[{title:"8",key:1,correct:""},{title:"2",key:2,correct:""},{title:"NaN",key:3,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:4,correct:""},{title:"6",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const numbers = [ 2009, 95, 262 ];\nconst [ first, ...rest ] = numbers;\nconst result = rest[ 1 ];",example:[{title:"95",key:1,correct:""},{title:"262",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const o = {\n  name: 'ECMAScript',\n  version: 2016,\n};\n\nconst result = Object.values( o ).join( '' );",example:[{title:"nameVersion",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"ECMAScript2016",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"[]",key:3,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = Number.parseInt( '1995 year' + 1 );",example:[{title:"1996",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""},{title:"1995",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"NaN",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let name = 1;\n( { name } = { name: 3 } );\nconst result = name;",example:[{title:"1",key:1,correct:""},{title:"3",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"NaN",key:3,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nlet result = 1;\n\nfor ( const value of array ) {\n  result *= value;\n}",example:[{title:"36",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""},{title:"36",key:3,correct:""},{title:"0",key:4,correct:""},{title:"6",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test3",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = Object.is(NaN,NaN);",example:[{title:"false",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let result = 2009;\nlet value = 262;\nconst obj = {\n  value:95\n};\nwith(obj) {\nresult = value;\n}\n",example:[{title:"95",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"262",key:1,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"var value = 2009;\ndelete value;\nconst result = value;",example:[{title:"2009",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"null",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = null && undefined;",example:[{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:2,correct:""},{title:"null",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const s = new Set([1,1,2,3,4,4,5,5]);\nconst result = s.size;",example:[{title:"7",key:1,correct:""},{title:"8",key:2,correct:""},{title:"4",key:3,correct:""},{title:"5",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = Number.MIN_VALUE > 0;",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = 'good' > 'bad';",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"false",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nconst map = (v, i) => v * i;",example:[{title:"[NaN,NaN,NaN]",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[1, 4, 9]",key:2,correct:""},{title:"[1, 2, 3]",key:3,correct:""},{title:"[0, 2, 6]",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test4",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const result = Number( "" ) + 1;',example:[{title:"1",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"0",key:1,correct:""},{title:"NaN",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const numbers = [ 2009 ];\nconst [ first, second = 95 ] = numbers;\n\nconst result = second;",example:[{title:"2009",key:1,correct:""},{title:"95",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:3,correct:""},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const value = 2009;\nconst result = isFinite( value );",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const func = new Function( 'a', 'b', 'return a+b;' );\nconst result = func( 1, 2 );",example:[{title:"3",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const func = (obj) => {\n  obj = null;\n};\nconst obj = {\n  name: 'Brendan'\n};\nfunc( obj );\n\nconst result = obj.name;",example:[{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"Brendan",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const firstArray = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nconst secondArray = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nconst result = firstArray === secondArray",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"true",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 3, 5, 3, 10 ];\nconst result = array.lastIndexOf( 3 );",example:[{title:"1",key:1,correct:""},{title:"0",key:2,correct:""},{title:"-1",key:3,correct:""},{title:"2",key:4,correct:""},{title:"3",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"function func() {\n  return;\n}\n\nconst result = func();",example:[{title:"undefined",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test5",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const value = 23.45;\nconst result = value.toFixed( 1 );",example:[{title:"23.45",key:1,correct:""},{title:"23.4",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"23.5",key:2,correct:""},{title:"23",key:3,correct:""},{title:"24",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"Array.prototype ì— ì¡´ì¬í•˜ì§€ ì•ŠëŠ” ë©”ì†Œë“œëŠ”?",example:[{title:"call",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"slice",key:1,correct:""},{title:"map",key:2,correct:""},{title:"forEach",key:3,correct:""},{title:"reduce",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nlet result = 0;\nfor ( const value in array ) {\n  result += +value;\n}",example:[{title:"3",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"6",key:1,correct:""},{title:"0012",key:2,correct:""},{title:"5",key:3,correct:""},{title:"0123",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let first = 262;\nlet second = 2009;\n\n[ first, second ] = [ second, first ];\n\nconst result =;",example:[{title:"262",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a TypeError",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [ 1, 2, 3 ];\nconst arrayNext = array;\narrayNext.length = 0;\n\nconst result = array[ 0 ];",example:[{title:"undefined",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"1",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"1,2,3",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const name = 'Brendan';\nconst obj = {\n  [ name ]: name\n};\n\nconst result = obj[ 'name' ];",example:[{title:"undefined",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"name",key:2,correct:""},{title:"Brendan",key:3,correct:""},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const name = 'Javascript';\nconst func = function () {\n  return this.name;\n};\nconst obj = {\n  name: 'ECMAScript',\n  func: func\n};\n\nconst result = obj.func();",example:[{title:"Javascript",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""},{title:"ECMAScript",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let result = 2009;\ntry {\n  result = 262;\n} finally {\n  result = 95;\n}",example:[{title:"95",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"262",key:1,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test6",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const SimpleNumber = function (value) {\n  return value;\n};\nconst number = new SimpleNumber( 2009 );\nconst result = number === 2009;",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"true",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const a = isFinite( null );\nconst b = Number.isFinite( null );\nconst result = a === b;\n",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"true",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let result = 0;\nfor ( let i = 0; i < 5; i++ ) {\n  if ( i % 2 ){\n    result += i;\n  }\n}\n",example:[{title:"6",key:1,correct:""},{title:"15",key:2,correct:""},{title:"0",key:3,correct:""},{title:"4",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"5",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let value = 2009;\nsetTimeout( () => {\n  value = 262;\n\n}, 0 );\nconst result = value;",example:[{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"262",key:2,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = '1' + 1;",example:[{title:"11",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"2",key:1,correct:""},{title:"NaN",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [1, 2, 3];\nconst result = array.unshift( 0 );",example:[{title:"[0,1,2,3]",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[1,2,3,0]",key:2,correct:""},{title:"4",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"[1,2,3]",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = typeof !!null;",example:[{title:"boolean",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"number",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:2,correct:""},{title:"false",key:3,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const User = function (name) {\n  this.name = name;\n};\n\nconst Brendan = new User( 'Brendan' );\nconst James = new Brendan.constructor( 'James' );\n\nconst result = James instanceof User;\n",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"false",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test7",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = true > false;",example:[{title:"false",key:1,correct:""},{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"number",key:2,correct:""},{title:"null",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = Number.isInteger( 95.0 );",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\nconst result = array.splice( 1, 2, 3 );\n",example:[{title:"[2,3]",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"[1,2,3,4,5,1,2,3]",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[1,1,2,2,3,3]",key:2,correct:""},{title:"[3,3,4,5]",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const func = () => {\n};\n\nconst result = func instanceof Object;\n",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const { name } = {\n  name: 'Brendan'\n};\n\nconst result = name;",example:[{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"name",key:3,correct:""},{title:"Brendan",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const items = [1, 2, 3, 4];\nconst noop = value => value;\n\nfor ( var i = 0; i < items.length; i++ ) {\n  noop( items[ i ] );\n}\n\nconst result = i;\n",example:[{title:"4",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"0",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let value = 32;\nconst reseult = value << 1;",example:[{title:"64",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"-32",key:1,correct:""},{title:"31",key:2,correct:""},{title:"16",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const str = 'JavaScript is not Java';\nconst result = str.replace( 'Java', 'ECMA' );",example:[{title:"ECMAScript is not Java",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"JavaScript is not ECMA",key:1,correct:""},{title:"ECMAScript is not ECMA",key:2,correct:""},{title:"JavaScript is not Java",key:3,correct:""},{title:"ECMA",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test8",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = (1 && 2) || (0 && 3);",example:[{title:"2",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"1",key:1,correct:""},{title:"0",key:2,correct:""},{title:"3",key:3,correct:""},{title:"4",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"var prop = 95;\nconst result = window.prop;",example:[{title:"true",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""},{title:"95",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const obj = {\n  value: 2009,\n};\nconst func = function () {\n  this.value = 262;\n};\n\nfunc.call( obj );\nconst result = obj.value;",example:[{title:"262",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"2009",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let prop = 95;\nconst result = window.prop;",example:[{title:"undefined",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"null",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:2,correct:""},{title:"true",key:3,correct:""},{title:"95",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const array = [5, 1, 3, 4, 2];\nconst result = array.some( (a, b) => b - a );",example:[{title:"[5,4,3,2,1]",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"[1,2,3,4,5]",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[5,1,3,4,2]",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const str = "{\\"name\\":\\"Brendan\\"}";\nconst json = JSON.parse( str );\nconst result = json.name;\n',example:[{title:"Brendan",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a ReferenceError",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const result = typeof Object;",example:[{title:"function",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"Object",key:1,correct:""},{title:"object",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a TypeError",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let result = 2009;\ntry {\n  result = 262 / 0;\n} catch (e) {\n  result = 0 / 262;\n}\n",example:[{title:"Infinity",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a TypeError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"0",key:2,correct:""},{title:"2009",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0}]}],advanced:[{name:"Test1",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const toString = Object.prototype.toString;\nconst result = toString.call(null);",example:[{title:"[object Null]",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"[object Object]",key:1,correct:""},{title:"[Object]",key:2,correct:""},{title:"Null",key:3,correct:""},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const func = function(){\n  return arguments.join("");\n}\nconst result = func(2009,262);',example:[{title:"2271",key:0,correct:""},{title:"2009262",key:1,correct:""},{title:"NaN",key:2,correct:""},{title:"throw a TypeError",key:3,correct:"correct"}],correct:3},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'let result = "string";\n(function (){\n  result = typeof arguments;\n})();',example:[{title:"undefined",key:0,correct:""},{title:"null",key:1,correct:""},{title:'"array"',key:2,correct:""},{title:'"object"',key:3,correct:"correct"},{title:'"string"',key:4,correct:""}],correct:3},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const target = {\n  name : "ECMAScript"\n}\n\nconst proxy = new Proxy(target, {});\nproxy.name = "Javascript";\n\nconst result = target.name;',example:[{title:"ECMAScript",key:0,correct:""},{title:"Javascript",key:1,correct:"correct"},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"Null",key:3,correct:""},{title:"null",key:4,correct:""}],correct:1},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const User = function () {\n  const result = new.target === User;\n};\n\nconst man = new User();",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const  constructor = function () {};\n\nconst result = constructor.prototype.constructor == constructor;",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:""},{title:"true",key:1,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""}],correct:1},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const plus = +0;\nconst minus = -0;\nconst result = Object.is( plus, minus );",example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:""},{title:"false",key:1,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""}],correct:1},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'const obj={};\nconst result = "toString" in obj;',example:[{title:"true",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"false",key:1,correct:""},{title:"null",key:2,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:3,correct:""}],correct:0}]},{name:"Test2",data:[{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const params = [1, 2, 3, 4, 5];\nconst result = Math.max.apply(10,params);",example:[{title:"5",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"10",key:3,correct:""},{title:"6",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:'function func(a, b) {\n  "use strict";\n  a = 262;\n  b = 95;\n  const result = arguments[ 1 ];\n};\n\nfunc( 95, 262 );',example:[{title:"undefined",key:1,correct:""},{title:"throw a SyntaxError",key:2,correct:""},{title:"1",key:3,correct:""},{title:"262",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"95",key:4,correct:""}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"let value = 10;\nconst promise = new Promise( (resolve) => {\n  value = 20;\n  resolve( 30 );\n} );\nconst result = value;\n",example:[{title:"30",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""},{title:"10",key:3,correct:""},{title:"0",key:4,correct:""},{title:"20",key:0,correct:"correct"}],correct:0},{question:"result ì˜ ê°’ì€?",code:"const object = new Object();\nconst proto = Object.getPrototypeOf( object );\n\nconst result = proto instanceof Object;",example:[{title:"false",key:0,correct:"correct"},{title:"true",key:1,correct:""},{title:"undefined",key:2,correct:""}],correct:0}]}]},l=n;t.a=l,(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(c.register(n,"questions","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\data\\questions.js"),c.register(l,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\data\\questions.js")),(o="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&o(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},35:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){r.d(t,"a",(function(){return p}));var c,o=r(0),n=r.n(o),l=r(21),a=r(52),i=r(5),s=r(11);(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);var u="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature:function(e){return e},d=function(e){var t=e.history,r=Object(i.b)(),c=Object(i.c)((function(e){return e.main}),[]).level;Object(o.useEffect)((function(){var e=l.a.getLocalStorage(s.b);e&&Object.keys(e).length||(l.a.setLocalStorage(s.b,{}),e={}),r(Object(s.e)({scores:e}))}),[c]);return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement(a.a,{onClick:function(e){var r=e.target.dataset.level;t.push("/level/".concat(r))}}))};u(d,"useDispatch{dispatch}\nuseSelector{{ level }}\nuseEffect{}",(function(){return[i.b,i.c]}));var y,f,p=function(e){var t=e.title,r=void 0===t?s.a:t,c=e.index,o=e.onClickScoreReset;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},n.a.createElement("h2",{className:"title"},r),c===s.c&&n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-reset",onClick:o},"ì ìˆ˜ ì´ˆê¸°í™”"))},k=d;t.b=k,(y="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(y.register(d,"MainContainer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\MainContainer.jsx"),y.register(p,"Header","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\MainContainer.jsx"),y.register(k,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\MainContainer.jsx")),(f="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&f(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},44:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c,o=r(0),n=r.n(o),l=(r(69),r(71),r(57)),a=r(9),i=r(15),s=r(45),u=r(5),d=r(35),y=r(53),f=r(54),p=r(55);(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var k,b,m=Object(i.createStore)(y.a,Object(s.composeWithDevTools)()),v=function(){return n.a.createElement(u.a,{store:m},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},n.a.createElement(d.a,null),n.a.createElement(l.a,null,n.a.createElement(a.c,null,n.a.createElement(a.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",component:d.b}),n.a.createElement(a.a,{path:"/level/:level/quiz/:index",component:p.a}),n.a.createElement(a.a,{path:"/level/:level",component:f.a})))))},g=v;t.a=g,(k="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(k.register(m,"store","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\App.jsx"),k.register(v,"App","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\App.jsx"),k.register(g,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\App.jsx")),(b="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&b(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},52:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c,o=r(0),n=r.n(o);(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var l,a,i=function(e){var t=e.onClick;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"contents"},n.a.createElement(s,{title:d,contents:f,level:u.INTERMEDIATE,onClick:t}),n.a.createElement(s,{title:y,contents:p,level:u.ADVANCED,onClick:t}))},s=function(e){var t=e.title,r=e.contents,c=e.onClick,o=e.level;return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"card"},n.a.createElement("h3",null,t),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"main_text"},n.a.createElement("p",null,r.split("\n").map((function(e,t){return n.a.createElement("span",{key:t},e,n.a.createElement("br",null))})))),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn",onClick:c,"data-level":o},"ì‹œì‘"))},u={INTERMEDIATE:"intermediate",ADVANCED:"advanced"},d="ê¸°ì´ˆë¬¸ì œ",y="ì¤‘ê¸‰ë¬¸ì œ",f="ê¸°ì´ˆì…ë‹ˆë‹¤!. \n ë¬¸ì œë¥¼ ë³´ê³  ë§ëŠ” ë‹µì„ ê³¨ë¼ì£¼ì„¸ìš”.",p="ì¡°ê¸ˆ ì–´ë ¤ìš´ ì¤‘ê¸‰ë¬¸ì œì…ë‹ˆë‹¤. \n ë¬¸ì œë¥¼ ë³´ê³  ë§ëŠ” ë‹µì„ ê³¨ë¼ì£¼ì„¸ìš”.",k=i;t.a=k,(l="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(l.register(i,"LevelContainer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(s,"QuestionCard","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(u,"LEVEL","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(d,"titleLevel1","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(y,"titleLevel2","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(f,"contentsLevel1","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(p,"contentsLevel2","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx"),l.register(k,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\LevelContainer.jsx")),(a="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&a(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},53:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c,o=r(15),n=r(11);(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var l,a,i=Object(o.combineReducers)({main:n.d}),s=i;t.a=s,(l="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(l.register(i,"rootReducer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\index.js"),l.register(s,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\reducers\\index.js")),(a="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&a(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},54:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c,o=r(0),n=r.n(o),l=r(28),a=r(5);(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);var i="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature:function(e){return e},s=function(e){var t=e.match,r=e.history,c=Object(a.c)((function(e){return e.main})).scores,o=void 0===c?{}:c,i=t.params.level,s=l.a[i],u=function(e){var c=e.target.dataset.order;r.push("".concat(t.url,"/quiz/").concat(c))};return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"items"},s.map((function(e,t){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"item",key:e.name},n.a.createElement("h3",null,e.name),n.a.createElement("p",null,"ì ìˆ˜ :"," ",o[i]&&o[i][t]?o[i][t]:0,"ì "),n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn",onClick:u,"data-order":t},"ì‹œ ì‘"))}))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"back"},n.a.createElement("button",{className:"btn btn-back",onClick:function(){r.push("/")}},"ì²˜ìŒìœ¼ë¡œ")))};i(s,"useSelector{{ scores = {} }}",(function(){return[a.c]}));var u,d,y=s;t.a=y,(u="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(u.register(s,"QuestionListContainer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\QuestionListContainer.jsx"),u.register(y,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\QuestionListContainer.jsx")),(d="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&d(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},55:function(e,t,r){"use strict";(function(e){var c,o=r(0),n=r.n(o),l=(r(77),r(36)),a=r.n(l),i=r(56),s=r.n(i),u=r(28),d=r(11),y=r(5);function f(e,t){var r=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var c=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(c=c.filter((function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable}))),r.push.apply(r,c)}return r}function p(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var r=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?f(Object(r),!0).forEach((function(t){k(e,t,r[t])})):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(r)):f(Object(r)).forEach((function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(r,t))}))}return e}function k(e,t,r){return t in e?Object.defineProperty(e,t,{value:r,enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0}):e[t]=r,e}function b(e){return function(e){if(Array.isArray(e)){for(var t=0,r=new Array(e.length);t<e.length;t++)r[t]=e[t];return r}}(e)||m(e)||function(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to spread non-iterable instance")}()}function m(e){if(Symbol.iterator in Object(e)||"[object Arguments]"===Object.prototype.toString.call(e))return Array.from(e)}function v(e,t){return x(e)||function(e,t){if(!(Symbol.iterator in Object(e)||"[object Arguments]"===Object.prototype.toString.call(e)))return;var r=[],c=!0,o=!1,n=void 0;try{for(var l,a=e[Symbol.iterator]();!(c=(l=a.next()).done)&&(r.push(l.value),!t||r.length!==t);c=!0);}catch(e){o=!0,n=e}finally{try{c||null==a.return||a.return()}finally{if(o)throw n}}return r}(e,t)||g()}function g(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to destructure non-iterable instance")}function x(e){if(Array.isArray(e))return e}(c="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&c(e);var j="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature:function(e){return e},h=function(e){var t=e.match,r=e.history,c=t.params,l=c.level,i=c.index,f=u.a[l][i].data,k=void 0===f?[]:f,j=Object(y.c)((function(e){return e.main})).scores,h=v(Object(o.useState)(0),2),q=h[0],E=h[1],O=v(Object(o.useState)(k[q]),2),w=O[0],S=O[1],H=v(Object(o.useState)(!1),2),G=H[0],C=H[1],N=v(Object(o.useState)("ë‹¤ìŒë¬¸ì œ"),2),D=N[0],M=N[1],A=Object(y.b)(),T=k.length-1,P=Object(o.useRef)(0);Object(o.useEffect)((function(){a.a.registerLanguage("javascript",s.a),document.querySelectorAll("pre code").forEach((function(e){a.a.highlightBlock(e)}))}),[w]);var I=function(e,t){var r,c=b(e.example).map((function(e){return+e.key==+t?p({},e,{correct:"wrong"}):e}));return p({},e,{example:(x(r=c)||m(r)||g()).slice(0)})},J=Object(o.useCallback)((function(e){var t=e.target.dataset.select;C(!0),t&&!G&&(+w.correct==+t?P.current=P.current+1:S(I(w,t)))}),[G]),R=Object(o.useCallback)((function(){var e=q+1;if(T===e&&M("ì±„ì í•˜ê¸°"),T<e)return P.current===k.length?alert("ë§Œì !"):alert("".concat(T+1,"ê°œ ì¤‘ ").concat(P.current,"ê°œ ë§ì•˜ìŠµë‹ˆë‹¤!!")),void _(P.current/k.length*100);C(!1),E(e),S(k[e])}),[q]),_=Object(o.useCallback)((function(e){var t=p({},j);j[l]&&null!==i||(t[l]=[]),t[l][i]=e,A(Object(d.e)({scores:t})),r.push("/level/".concat(l))}),[j]);return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question_container"},n.a.createElement(L,{data:w,onClick:J,isSelect:G,onClickNext:R,btnText:D,lastIndex:T,curIndex:q}))};j(h,"useSelector{{ scores }}\nuseState{[curIndex, setCurIndex](0)}\nuseState{[curQuestion, setCurQuestion](data[curIndex])}\nuseState{[isSelected, setIsSelected](false)}\nuseState{[btnText, setBtnText]('ë‹¤ìŒë¬¸ì œ')}\nuseDispatch{dispatch}\nuseRef{matchCount}\nuseEffect{}\nuseCallback{onClick}\nuseCallback{onClickNext}\nuseCallback{updateScore}",(function(){return[y.c,y.b]}));var q,E,L=function(e){var t=e.data,r=e.onClick,c=e.isSelect,o=e.onClickNext,l=e.btnText,a=e.lastIndex,i=e.curIndex,s=t.question,u=t.code,d=t.example;return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question"},"ğŸ’» ","".concat(i+1,"/").concat(a+1,". ").concat(s)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"code"},n.a.createElement("pre",null,n.a.createElement("code",{className:"javascript"},u))),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answers"},d.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer ".concat(c?e.correct:""),"data-select":e.key,key:e.key,onClick:r},e.title)})),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"next"},c&&n.a.createElement("button",{className:"next-btn",onClick:o,"data-reset":l},l))))},O=h;t.a=O,(q="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&(q.register(h,"QuestionContainer","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\QuestionContainer.jsx"),q.register(L,"Question","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\QuestionContainer.jsx"),q.register(O,"default","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\containers\\QuestionContainer.jsx")),(E="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&E(e)}).call(this,r(1)(e))},63:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(64)},64:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t),function(e){var t,c=r(0),o=r.n(c),n=r(22),l=r.n(n),a=r(62),i=r(44);(t="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.enterModule:void 0)&&t(e);"undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal&&reactHotLoaderGlobal.default.signature;var s,u,d=Object(a.hot)(i.a);l.a.render(o.a.createElement(d,null),document.querySelector("#root")),(s="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.default:void 0)&&s.register(d,"Hot","D:\\project\\react-js-question\\src\\index.jsx"),(u="undefined"!=typeof reactHotLoaderGlobal?reactHotLoaderGlobal.leaveModule:void 0)&&u(e)}.call(this,r(1)(e))},69:function(e,t,r){var c=r(30),o=r(70);"string"==typeof(o=o.__esModule?o.default:o)&&(o=[[e.i,o,""]]);var n={insert:"head",singleton:!1},l=(c(e.i,o,n),o.locals?o.locals:{});e.exports=l},70:function(e,t,r){(t=r(31)(!1)).push([e.i,"html, body, h1, h2, h3, h4, h5, h6, p, blockquote, code, img, dl, dt, dd, ol, ul, li, fieldset, legend, caption { margin: 0; padding: 0; border: 0; }\r\ndiv, span, article, section, header, footer, p, ul, li, fieldset, legend, label, a, nav { box-sizing: border-box; }\r\nhtml {\r\n    height: 100%;\r\n}\r\nbody {\r\n    min-height: 100%;\r\n}\r\nhtml, body, div, span, applet, object, iframe,\r\nh1, h2, h3, h4, h5, h6, p, blockquote, pre,\r\na, abbr, acronym, address, big, cite, code,\r\ndel, dfn, em, img, ins, kbd, q, s, samp,\r\nsmall, strike, strong, sub, sup, tt, var,\r\nb, u, i, center,\r\ndl, dt, dd, ol, ul, li,\r\nfieldset, form, label, legend,\r\ntable, caption, tbody, tfoot, thead, tr, th, td,\r\narticle, aside, canvas, details, embed,\r\nfigure, figcaption, footer, header, hgroup,\r\nmenu, nav, output, ruby, section, summary,\r\ntime, mark, audio, video {\r\n    margin: 0;\r\n    padding: 0;\r\n    border: 0;\r\n}\r\narticle, aside, details, figcaption, figure,\r\nfooter, header, hgroup, menu, nav, section {\r\n    display: block;\r\n}\r\nol,\r\nul {\r\n    list-style: none;\r\n}\r\ntable {\r\n    border-collapse: collapse;\r\n    border-spacing: 0;\r\n}\r\n",""]),e.exports=t},71:function(e,t,r){var c=r(30),o=r(72);"string"==typeof(o=o.__esModule?o.default:o)&&(o=[[e.i,o,""]]);var n={insert:"head",singleton:!1},l=(c(e.i,o,n),o.locals?o.locals:{});e.exports=l},72:function(e,t,r){(t=r(31)(!1)).push([e.i,"body{\r\n    background: rgb(25, 32, 36);\r\n}\r\n.container{\r\n    max-width: 500px;\r\n    margin: 0 auto;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.header{\r\n    position: relative;\r\n    background-color: rgb(61, 78, 85);\r\n    padding: 10px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.header .title{\r\n    color: white;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.contents{\r\n    width: 100%;\r\n    height: 100vh;\r\n    justify-content: center;\r\n    box-sizing: border-box;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.card{\r\n    position: relative;\r\n    min-height: 150px;\r\n    padding: 20px;\r\n    margin-top: 10px;\r\n    background: white;\r\n    border-radius: 5px;\r\n    box-sizing: border-box;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.btn{\r\n    position: absolute;\r\n    width: 100px;\r\n    height: 30px;\r\n    padding: 5px;\r\n    bottom: 10px;\r\n    border-style: none;\r\n    border-radius: 5px;\r\n    background-color: rgb(38, 50, 56);\r\n    color: white;\r\n    cursor: pointer;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.back{\r\n    position: relative;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.btn-back{\r\n    top: 10px;\r\n    right: 0;\r\n    margin: 0 auto;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.btn-reset{\r\n    position: absolute;\r\n    right: 10px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n\r\n/*ë¦¬ìŠ¤íŠ¸*/\r\n.items{\r\n    display: grid;\r\n    grid-template-columns: repeat(2,auto);\r\n    grid-gap: 1rem;\r\n   padding-top: 10px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.item{\r\n    position: relative;\r\n    height: 100px;\r\n    background: white;\r\n    border-radius: 5px;\r\n    padding: 5px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n/*ë¬¸ì œ*/\r\n.question_container{\r\n    background-color: rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.46);\r\n    color: black;\r\n    border-radius: 0 0 5px 5px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.question{\r\n    padding: 10px;\r\n    background: white;\r\n}\r\n\r\n\r\n.answer{\r\n    height: 50px;\r\n    margin-bottom: 2px;\r\n    padding-left: 10px;\r\n    box-sizing: border-box;\r\n    background: white;\r\n    line-height: 50px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.main_text{\r\n    padding: 10px;\r\n    line-height: 1.5rem;\r\n}\r\n\r\n\r\n.next{\r\n    position: relative;\r\n    height: 60px;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.next-btn{\r\n    position: absolute;\r\n    right: 10px;\r\n    top: 5px;\r\n    width: 100px;\r\n    height: 40px;\r\n    border-style: none;\r\n    border-radius: 5px;\r\n    background-color: rgb(38, 50, 56);\r\n    color: white;\r\n    cursor: pointer;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.correct{\r\n    background: yellowgreen;\r\n}\r\n\r\n.wrong{\r\n    background: red;\r\n}\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\n",""]),e.exports=t}});